(Hey! Hey!)
Red cape on and spikes up high
Tiny feet, but watch me fly
Something big is on the road
I point my paw and say "Go home!"
Spin it, spin it, magic in my hand
One, two, three, and
Out of my way! Out of my way!
I'm the little boss today
Pop, pop, pop, they float away
Out of my way! Out of my way!
A dragon roaring on the hill
A wobbly jelly, never still
A grumpy giant in the way
I stamp my foot, he runs away
Spin it, spin it, magic in my hand
One, two, three, and
Out of my way! Out of my way!
I'm the little boss today
Pop, pop, pop, they float away
Out of my way! Out of my way!
Who's the boss? (Me!)
Little spikes and a big red cape
Who's the boss? (Me! Me! Me!)
Sun goes down, I'm walking home
Panda, Fox and Camel know
Who was brave and who was best
Okay... maybe now I'll rest
(Hey! Hey!)
Out of my way! Out of my way!
I'm the little boss today
Pop, pop, pop, they float away
See you tomorrow! Out of my way!
Out of my way!